Noy Ben David // Software Engineer

Profile

Innovative Software Engineer with ability to quickly grasp new languages, systems, and frameworks. **Experienced** in developing in **Java**, **C#**, **Python**, **C++**. Able to effectively prioritize, multitask, and perform well in a fast-paced environment.

Have Deep knowledge in **object-oriented programming** and Modules. **Strong problem-solving** skills along with the ability to work independently.

Work experience

09/2019 - 04/2021

Team Leader Shufersal Ltd.

- Handled, prioritized and problem-solved multiple tasks connected to the project called "Tav Hazahav".
- Worked with management on strategic initiatives, facilitating cross-department alignment.

02/2016 - 08/2018 TEL AVIV

Supervisor Service Representative Tel Aviv Municipality

- Supported Customer Services Associates with accurate financial services information (money transfers, bill payments, etc.)
- Functional understanding of CRM material, account and customer data.

Education

10/2018 - 10/2021

Computer Science | B.Sc.

Grade point average: 87

Working knowledge in Android app Development Experience in modern web development practices and methodologies Knowledge in testing and debugging processes

Skills

- SOFTWARE SKILLS

Java
C#
Python
SQL
Jenkins
Firebase/MongoDB
C++



– SOFT SKILLS Public Speaker Team player Accountable Problem-solving

Volunteering

06/2017 — PRESENT

Pitchon Lev (Non-profit)

Aid and Support center weekly volunteering activity, providing family packages to those in need.

Languages

English Full Hebrew Native